tunnel2towers.org 2016-11-30

# Stephen Siller Tunnel to Towers Foundation Donor Privacy Policy

                            Stephen Siller Tunnel to Towers Foundation
                                              Donor Privacy Policy
Commitment to Privacy
The Stephen Siller Tunnel to Towers Foundation (“Tunnel to Towers”) is deeply committed to
protecting the privacy of our donors and safeguarding all personal information.
Personal Information
Personal information refers to any information that identifies you personally, such as first and
last names, home addresses, e-mail addresses, phone numbers, payment information such as
bank account and credit card numbers, and the like.
Safeguards & Use of Personal Information
Every reasonable precaution shall be taken to protect and preserve the confidentiality of our
donors’ personal information. All employees, agents and authorized service providers of Tunnel
to Towers are required to keep all information secure.
Tunnel to Towers ensures that all personal information is properly collected, used only for the
purposes for which it is collected, and is disposed of in a secure and timely manner when it is no
longer needed.
Any information supplied by donors to Tunnel to Towers will be used solely to fulfill their
donation and purpose identified by donors. All requests to remain anonymous shall be honored.
Sharing or Selling of Personal Information
Tunnel to Towers will not share, sell, trade or rent a donor’s personal information to others. This
applies to all donor information, whether collected offline or online, and pertains to all contents
of donor files.
Tunnel to Towers will not send you donor mailings on behalf of other organizations.
Online Collection of Information
Stephen Siller Tunnel To Towers Foundation - Donor Privacy Policy
Updated November 2015

Tunnel to Towers has procedures in place to safeguard and secure the information collected
online. Tunnel to Towers does not collect personal information of those who visit our website.
There are numerous safeguards in place to protect the security of credit card transactions.
Technologies and processes such as encryption, access controls, network firewalls, and physical
security are in place. Our Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software is the industry standard and
among the best software available today for secure commerce transactions. It encrypts all of your
personal information so that it cannot be read over the internet.
Communications Directly from Tunnel to Towers
From time to time, Tunnel to Towers will send announcements, invitations and
foundation/program updates via email and/or regular mail.
Supporters may choose to opt out at any time, which will cease all communications from us. You
may unsubscribe from our e-mail list by using the unsubscribe link at the bottom of our
newsletter emails or contact us through our postal address: 2361 Hylan Blvd., Staten Island, NY
10306. You may also unsubscribe from regular mailings using such postal address.
External Links
At times, there may be links to other sites or servers that are not operated by Tunnel to Towers.
These are links that do not fall under our domain. Tunnel to Towers takes no responsibility for,
and exercises no control over, the organizations, views, or accuracy of the information contained
on outside servers. If you visit one of these linked sites, you should review their privacy policy
for Tunnel to Towers is not responsible for practices of other companies.
Changes to our Privacy Policy
It may be necessary for Tunnel to Towers to change this Privacy Policy from time to time. When
we do, we will note the last update at the bottom of this Privacy Policy. Any changes will not be
retroactively applied and will not alter how we handle previously collected information.
For changes on this policy that may be materially less restrictive on use or disclosure of
personally identifiable information, Tunnel To Towers will obtain your consent before
implementing the change by sending a notice to your primary email address and home address
specified in our records and by placing a prominent notice on our website.
Stephen Siller Tunnel To Towers Foundation - Donor Privacy Policy
Updated November 2015
